(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-07T22:46:16.070481",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Thank you all for joining us today for Baelz Hakos Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone,
but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome.
We'd love it if you could share them online to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
皆様 本日はハコス・ベールズ生誕祭2026に
Thank you all very much for coming
お越しくださいまして 誠にありがとうございます
to Hakos Baelz Birthday Celebration 2026 today.
開演に先立ちまして
Prior to the performance,
皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます
we have a few requests and announcements for everyone.
テレビやパソコン スマートフォンの前では飲食は可能ですが
You may eat and drink in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but
キーボードにこぼさないように気をつけてください
please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは #ReCOLOR3D です
The hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
SNSでたくさんポストしてください
Please post a lot on social media.
開演中 カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です
Taking photos with a camera or smartphone during the show is very welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上がっていただけますと幸いです
We'd be glad if you post a lot and get excited together.
それでは 開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the show begins.
Thank you all for joining us today for Baelz Hakos Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone,
but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome.
We'd love it if you could share them online to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
皆様 本日はハコス・ベールズ生誕祭2026に
Thank you all very much for coming
お越しくださいまして 誠にありがとうございます
to Hakos Baelz Birthday Celebration 2026 today.
開演に先立ちまして
Prior to the performance,
皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます
we have a few requests and announcements for everyone.
テレビやパソコン スマートフォンの前では飲食は可能ですが
You may eat and drink in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but
キーボードにこぼさないように気をつけてください
please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは #ReCOLOR3D です
The hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
SNSでたくさんポストしてください
Please post a lot on social media.
開演中 カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です
Taking photos with a camera or smartphone during the show is very welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上がっていただけますと幸いです
We'd be glad if you post a lot and get excited together.
それでは 開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the show begins.
winning the soul
光の速さで
At the speed of light,
駆け抜ける衝動は
this impulse racing through—
何を犠牲にしても
no matter what I have to sacrifice,
叶えたい強さの覚悟が
I'm resolved with the strength to make it come true.
一度きりの
On this once-in-a-lifetime...
この瞬間にかけてみろ
...moment, take a chance on it!
自分を信じて
Believe in yourself.
時には運だって必要と言うのなら
If you say that luck is also needed at times,
宿命の旋律も
then even the melody of fate...
引き寄せて見せよう
...I'll show you I can pull it in!
走れ今を まだ終われない
Run through the present! It can't end yet!
辿り着きたい場所があるから
Because there's a place I want to reach!
その先へと進め
Press forward beyond it!
涙さえも強く胸に抱きしめ
Embracing even my tears tightly in my chest,
そこから始まるストーリー
the story that starts from there...
果てしなく続く
...continues without end!
winning the soul
掴め今を変えたいなら
Seize it! If you want to change the present,
描いた夢を未来に掲げ
hold up the dream you drew toward the future!
恐れないで挑め
Don't be afraid, challenge it!
走れ今を まだ終われない
Run through the present! It can't end yet!
辿り着きたい場所があるから
Because there's a place I want to reach!
その先へと進め
Press forward beyond it!
涙さえも強く胸に抱きしめ
Embracing even my tears tightly in my chest,
そこから始まるストーリー
the story that starts from there...
果てしなく続く
...continues without end!
winning the soul
Woh-oh, woh-oh, woh-oh
What's up, everyone!
I am Chaos, the End of Days,
Earth's real-life track-tuning cage device,
your best friend, Baelz Hakos from hololive English -Promise-!
我はカオス、終わりの果て The End。
I am Chaos, the ultimate end, The End.
降臨の輪舞曲、漆黒の薔薇。
The waltz of advent, the pitch-black rose.
汝の魂、
Thy soul,
破滅の... ハコス・ベールズです！
of ruin... I am Hakos Baelz!
Witness me!
Ah, another year, another Not Birthday Live!
Thank you so much for coming, everyone!
Did you like the opening act?
The opening show?
Thank you so much for coming, everyone!
This year, we have a Not Birthday Birthday Live again,
called ReCOLOR 3D!
That is also the hashtag, please use it, #ReCOLOR3D.
I don't know, it might be... the theme this year was "Color" for many reasons.
There's also a lot of special things that are happening today.
As you may or may not already know,
there's a lot of new things being revealed in this Live!
Maybe a new song?
Maybe a new outfit?
I don't know! You're just gonna have to wait and see!
えーっと、今年も誕生日じゃない誕生日ライブ
Um, this year too, I wanted to do a Not-Birthday Birthday Live,
やりたいと思います！ みんな来てくれてありがとうございます！
so here we are! Thank you so much for coming, everyone!
えー、今日のライブでね、
Um, in today's live,
新しいものいっぱいあると思いますので、
I think there are lots of new things,
最後まで観てくれたら嬉しいです！
so I'd be really happy if you watch until the end!
あー、もう疲れてる。やばい。
Ah, I'm already tired. Oh no.
はい！
Alright!
あの、ハッシュタグも、
Um, as for the hashtag as well,
ぜひぜひ、いっぱいコメントと写真をポストしてください！
please, please post lots of comments and pictures!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
Um, it is my birthday—not birthday,
but I'm just so excited to be able to share this day with all of you.
Once I catch my breath, we're gonna get this party started, yeah?
じゃあ、最後まで楽しんでいってください！
So, please enjoy yourselves until the very end!
そこ、次の曲ね、ちょっと...
Now, for the next song, I'm gonna go...
I'm gonna go to the other stage for the next song,
so I'll see you guys there, all right?
I'm gonna go now. Is that all right?
Okay, bye! See you guys there!
Race you!
あれが正解なんて
If that's supposed to be correct...
誰の成れの果て？
Whose tragic end is this?
答えも欲しいのも1個ってこれだけ
I only want one answer, and this is it.
悩んだってしょうがないじゃんね
There's no point in worrying, right?
あれは夢だったって思うことにしたって
Even if I decide it was all just a dream,
でも全然思えないんだけど助けてよフォロワー
I can't feel that way at all, help me out, followers.
抗うだけ若さに負け
Only resisting, losing to youth,
next, next, lucky, lucky, lucky!
アーリオ 割り切れたらさ オーリオ 楽なのにとか
If I could just split it, it'd be so easy...
aah-hmm もうヤダ
Aah-hmm, I hate this already.
なんて新世界か
What kind of new world is this?
あなた以外は あなた以外はいらないないない
Besides you, besides you, I don't need anyone else.
張らないでよバリア
Don't put up a barrier.
あるはずのかなにかあったならば
If there was something that was supposed to be there,
happy! jumpin’ yeah!
Happy! Jumpin' yeah!
あなたのその手とあたしこの手を
Your hand and this hand of mine,
繋いだらもう二度と離さないわ
once connected, I'll never let go again.
あなたのその手があたしこの手を
If your hand holds this hand of mine,
掴んだら以後お見知りおきを my love
please keep me in mind from now on, my love.
これで終わりなんて
Saying this is the end...
アガれないままなんて
Staying unhyped like this...
どうにかなっちゃえって願って願ってねぇ
Wishing and wishing that something happens, hey,
朝帰りしたりしちゃうん？どう？
shall we stay out until morning? How about it?
なあもう我慢できん
Hey, I can't hold back anymore.
pain, pain 痛いってば everyday
Pain, pain, I say it hurts every day.
まーゆーていけるけどな
Well, I can manage though.
ブルベ夏なんで関係ないな
I'm cool-summer skin tone, so it doesn't matter.
誰よりもネコ
More of a cat than anyone,
節操ないも結構
lack of principles is fine too.
あーしはあーしだ見といてよ ready
I am who I am, keep your eyes on me, ready.
もう今日で終わらせたいなって
Thinking I want to end it today,
リスタートできたらって
wishing I could restart...
でも無理よもう
But it's impossible now.
what’s on your mind?
What's on your mind?
アーリオ 割り切れたらさ オーリオ 楽なのにとか
If I could just split it, it'd be so easy...
aah-hmm もうヤダ
Aah-hmm, I hate this already.
なんて新世界か
What kind of new world is this?
あなた以外は あなた以外はいらないないない
Besides you, besides you, I don't need anyone else.
張らないでよバリア
Don't put up a barrier.
あるはずのかなにかあったならば
If there was something that was supposed to be there,
happy! jumpin’ yeah!
Happy! Jumpin' yeah!
あなたのその手とあたしこの手を
Your hand and this hand of mine,
繋いだらもう二度と離さないわ
once connected, I'll never let go again.
あなたのその手があたしこの手を
If your hand holds this hand of mine,
掴んだら以後お見知りおきを my love
please keep me in mind from now on, my love.
Na na na... Wow...
Oh, 以後お見知りおきを my love
Oh, please keep me in mind from now on, my love.
ラ・ディー・ラ・リー・ラ・ラ ラ・ディー・ラ
La dee la ree la la, la dee la
HEY!
Break away, Break away 細胞レベル
Break away, break away, down to the cellular level
I don't need 不本意 現状 憂えてる
I don't need unwillingly fretting over the status quo
姿仕草滑稽でしょう
Your look and gestures are ridiculous, right?
Don't you think? Don't you think?
I'm so lazy たぶんそう
I'm so lazy, probably so
Fine sound 並べてるだけの人
Just someone lining up fine sounds
Trash, crash, toss away
Don't you think? Don't you think?
In this world この頭には
In this world, inside this head,
What a beautiful 舞い散る花びら
what a beautiful sight, flower petals dancing down
バラライカ 飲みみたいな
like drinking a Balalaika.
ラ・ディー・ラ・リー・ラ・ラ ラ・ディー・ラ
La dee la ree la la, la dee la
誰もが大体
Everyone is pretty much...
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に
To a fleeting emotion,
Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
心は 95
My heart is at 95,
狂気のサムライ
a samurai of madness.
血走らせた目で
With bloodshot eyes,
引くくらい ready to die
enough to make you recoil, ready to die.
ハロー 日は昇り
Hello, the sun rises,
あなたの空 真っ黒な空
your sky, a pitch-black sky.
荒々しく 引き千切って
Roughly tearing it to shreds,
ほら その場所で 聞こえてくる 鼓動の仕掛け
look, right in that place, you can hear the mechanism of the heartbeat.
驚くのは まだこれから
It's too early to be surprised, the best is yet to come,
まだこれから
the best is yet to come.
あぁ もう待ちわびて
Ah, I'm tired of waiting.
時計の針 零時の街
Clock hands point to midnight in the city,
猛々しく 意気 raise your voice
fiercely spirited, raise your voice.
ほら すぐそこで 始まり出す 孤高の宴
Look, right over there, the solitary banquet begins.
奏でるのは オノレの調べ
What plays is your own melody,
唯一無二の オノレの調べ
one-and-only, your own melody.
ラ・ッダ・ッダ ラ・ッダ・ッダ
La da da, la da da
目の前に広がる 世界は blue
The world spreading before my eyes is blue,
ひとまず さあ move, move
for now, come on, move, move.
Speak about 生き方
Speak about your way of life,
There's no need 何をそんなに張り切って
there's no need, why get so worked up
偉そうに ah
and act so high and mighty, ah.
右も左も知リもしないで
Without knowing left or right,
言わないで Don't you think? Don't you think?
don't talk, don't you think? Don't you think?
ニヤリ 影が笑う
Smirking, the shadow laughs,
世界は大体
the world is mostly...
C-R-A-Z-Y
Tell me something for the new 偉大な期待の時代の到来
Tell me something for the new, the arrival of an era of grand expectations!
Clap back
Lose my mind, shooting my side
Say that あなたのその瞬間 Maybe Nothing wrong, nothing wrong
Say that... that moment of yours, maybe. Nothing wrong, nothing wrong.
La-di-da-di-rat-ta La-di-da!
誰もお題目
Everyone's chanting slogans!
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on a moment's emotion!
心もないのに
Without even a heart
陽気なサムライ
A cheerful samurai
血走らせた目でいく Drive, ready to die!
Drive with bloodshot eyes, ready to die!
荒れる火花 昇り あなたの空 まっ暗な空 あらあら 散る火花 ちぎって
Raging sparks rise up, into your sky, into pitch-black sky. Oh dear, tearing apart scattering sparks.
アハッ バカ
Aha, fool!
ほら その場所で 聞こえてくる言葉の仕掛け
Look, right at that spot, the trick of the words you hear...
驚くのは 誰 これから まだこれから
Who's going to be surprised? It's starting now, starting now!
あの街は
That town...
見て 時計の針 0時の街 たけてけ 敷く居座 Raise your voice
Look, clock hands, the town of midnight. Raise your voice!
ほら すぐそこで 始まりだす 本気の戯言
Look, right over there, starting up, serious nonsense!
華麗になれ 誇り高きあれ 唯一無二の 呪いの調べ
Be splendid! Be proud! The unique melody of a curse!
美 美 美にしろ注意
Be, be, be... Beware of that beauty.
あいつの信者は多い
She's got a lot of fanatics.
己を知りなさい bitch HDで映えるのに
Know yourself, bitch. You can see them all in HD.
私もしあわせみたいになりたい
Oh, I wanna look like you.
教えて教えて 幸せですよね？
Tell me, tell me, you must be happy, right?
もしこのまま消えたら愛されるのなら
If I disappear this way and end up being loved for it...
今すぐにでも綺麗に亡くなりたい
I would gladly die right now, beautifully.
こんなはずじゃないわ ダヴィンチ
This isn't how I should look, Da Vinci.
もう少しだけべっぴんに
Make me look just a little bit prettier.
コントラストも入れて頂戴
Add some contrast in there, too.
全世界を懲らしめたい
I wanna show the world how beautiful I am.
Look at this
Ah, look at this
Look at this 悲しいかも ayy, ayy, ayy
Look at this, it's a bit sad, ayy, ayy, ayy.
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Give my skin a bit more glow.
女盛り舐めたらヤイ
Don't mess with a woman in her prime, hey.
トイレに女神はおったんかい？
Did you find the goddess in the bathroom?
おったなら捕まえなさい
If you did, better catch her.
ちゃんみな最近マジかわいい
"Chanmina is so pretty nowadays."
わたくしは忘れないあの嵐
I'll never forget that storm.
あの時わたくしはまだ 17
Back then I was only seventeen.
あの時言ったよな
Remember what you said to me back then?
You can't be beautiful, you can't be famous
醜いブスが歌ってんじゃないよ
An ugly bitch like you shouldn't be a singer."
あの時狂った精神に才能が開花
As my mind grew insane back then, my talent blossomed.
味わった功も不功も一般じゃなかった
Every happiness and unhappiness I went through was unordinary.
本物を君は知るのかい？
Have you ever seen the real thing?
知識と経験のエロス
Eros of knowledge and experience.
まだ使いもんになってるかい？
Do you still have it in you?
女はみな正気じゃない
Women, we're all insane.
Ah, I'm beautiful!
Ow! Look at this!
Ah, look at this
Look at this! Look at this!
Look at this 悲しいかも ayy, ayy, ayy
Look at this, it's a bit sad, ayy, ayy, ayy.
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Give my skin a bit more glow.
女盛り舐めたらヤイ
Don't mess with a woman in her prime, hey.
トイレに女神はおったんかい？
Did you find the goddess in the bathroom?
おったなら捕まえなさい
If you did, better catch her.
Can you hear me Mina, are you the beauty?
Say July, you are the ma fucking beauty
Say July, you are the true fucking beauty.
予想違い驚きなさい
Be surprised, I'm not what you predicted.
磨いたらダイヤ 美しい
Polish me and I'm a diamond, beautiful.
悲観的？いや美学的
Pessimistic? No, aesthetical.
磨いたらダイヤ 美しい
Polish me and I'm a diamond, beautiful.
生きなさい 今見せなさい
Live and enchant right now.
あなたこそダイヤ 美しい
You are the diamond, beautiful.
I'm a fucking woman, and I'm fucking beautiful
God, here I am
We're fucking women, and we're fucking beautiful
Yeah!
Look everyone, I finally have a new outfit!
見て、見て、見て！新衣装！かわいい？どう？どう？どう？
Look, look, look! A new outfit! Isn't it cute? How is it? How is it? How is it?
悪気... あー、It's performance Bae!
Bad...? Ah, it's performance Bae!
You want to have a close-up? There's so many things I want to show off!
Starting from... let's start from the top down, from the head.
Look at that hair! Look at that fade!
かっこよくない？
Isn't it cool?
I asked for a wolf cut!
That's also half-up, half-down, so it's really easy to dance in.
めっちゃ踊りやすくて...
It's super easy to dance in...
かわいいでしょ？まあ可愛いかっこいい衣装。アハッ。
Cute, right? Well, a cute and cool outfit! Aha!
And then,
What else? What else? Oh, my makeup!
メイクも可愛いでしょ？
My makeup is cute too, right?
えへへへ〜
Ehehehe~
And then I have so many like hand accessories as well!
And then I have so many hand accessories as well!
Look at that!
Look how cool that is!
And then we'll do like a quick scan of the...
T-pose quick scan!
Quick scan of the body!
Woah! Woah!
There's also something very special.
I have an MC tail now.
If you noticed earlier, normally when I dance,
I have my tail just, you know, free, but...
You know, this is the MC resting tail,
cause the tail also needs resting periods as well.
So this is my MC tail!
Very cute! I hope you guys like it!
Oh my god, and this was designed by, of course, the amazing Mika-mama!
ありがとうございます！めっちゃくちゃ可愛いデザインになりました！ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much! It turned out to be such a super cute design! Thank you so much!
えへへへ
Ehehehe~
But...
That's not all!
I mean, if I get a new outfit, I feel like...
It's only fair that some other people get new outfits!
Come, come! 来て、来て、来て！
Come, come! Come, come, come!
Ah! The Bae dancers also get new outfits!
Ah! The Bae-dancers also get new outfits!
You get an outfit! You get an outfit! Everyone gets an outfit!
Look at them!
Oh, look at... Oh, so sexy! Oh!
So the Bae dancers have also upgraded outfits!
So the Bae-dancers also have upgraded outfits!
They have shorts with the boots, and the socks, and the jacket!
Wow, look at that! Amazing!
And then on the back of the jacket, they have my logo!
後ろにロゴもあります！
There's also my logo on the back!
Woah! 可愛い！
Woah! So cute!
I also...
Well, not designed, but I wanted the design to be easy for them to dance in as well, so...
This is the upgraded Bae Dance Team! Yeah!
と、可愛い！
And, cute!
ポーズ！
Pose!
可愛い！Yeah!
So cute! Yeah!
まあ、せっかくなんでね
Well, since we're here,
Since we all have new outfits, I think it's only fitting that we continue the rest of the live...
Like this! With our new outfits!
Oh!
じゃあ、踊りますか！
Well then, shall we dance?
We're gonna do the next song, uh, on the stage over there.
We're gonna do the next song on the stage over there.
行こう！
Let's go!
よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ...
Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho...
Woah!
緊張するな...
I'm getting nervous...
はい！じゃあ、どうぞ！
Alright! Here we go!
正体あらわせ
Reveal your true identity
月の光を飲む 僕の夜が来た
Swallowing moonlight, my night has arrived
けたたましく現れる one, two
Loudly making an appearance, one, two
危険を探して knock, knock, knock
Searching for danger, knock, knock, knock
Don't mess it up, forget it, make a finger
窓を見て you can see my-my eyes
Look through the window, you can see my-my eyes
その瞳に出会ったら
If you meet those eyes,
お前は仲間だ come come, say it
you are one of us, come come, say it
けしやうのものか ましやうのものか
Are you an apparition? A demonic entity?
正体あらわせ ayy, ta-da-da-da-da
Reveal your true identity, ayy, ta-da-da-da-da
変装して love it, 僕見て know it
Disguise yourself and love it, look at me and know it
らいらい らいら いや
Lie, lie, lie, lie, ya
明かせ love it, 存在 know it
Reveal it and love it, know its existence
いないいないいないばぁ
Peek-a-peek-a-peek-a-boo
Don't worry 傷つけないよ
Don't worry, I won't hurt you
ライアイア
Liar
I let you このミステリーに あいややややや
I let you into this mystery, ah-ya-ya-ya-ya
See this finger trap
明日は make it rough 今日は make it fire
Tomorrow make it rough, today make it fire
目を避けないで make it loud your voice
Don't look away, make your voice loud
よしよし 止せ 恐れ お狐様に任せよ！
There, there, stop being afraid, leave it to the Fox Spirit!
光を騙して作るんだ night
Deceive the light to create the night
あちこち目覚めて 闇が喝采
Awakening here and there, the darkness applauds
ねぇ ほら こっちおいで
Hey, come over here
Yeah, just shout out the spell
けしやうのものか ましやうのものか
Are you an apparition? A demonic entity?
正体あらわせ ayy, ta-da-da-da-da
Reveal your true identity, ayy, ta-da-da-da-da
未体験 love it, 僕たちは know it
An unexperienced love it, we know it
らいらい らいら いや
Lie, lie, lie, lie, ya
この世界変える see me
Changing this world, see me
期待 たい たい たいして
Look forward to it, look forward to it
Don't worry 傷つけないよ
Don't worry, I won't hurt you
ライアイア
Liar
I let you さあ 魑魅魍魎に あいややややや
I let you, now, into the evil spirits, ah-ya-ya-ya-ya
Hey, follow the queen fox
I'm the real master of this night
Hey, follow your queen fox
魅せられて dan-dan-dan
Mesmerized, dan-dan-dan
重なり合った 僕たちの show window
Overlapping, our show window
見透かすこの眼差し 君に届いてる？
Does this gaze seeing through you reach you?
Why don't you know, it's time now
どんな姿でも 構わない世界へ
To a world where it doesn't matter what form you take
けしやうのものか
Are you an apparition?
ましやうのものか
A demonic entity?
正体あらわせ
Reveal your true identity
Show your true colors
Yeah!
変装して love it 僕を見て know it / らいらい らいらい や
Disguise and love it, look at me and know it / Rai rai rai rai ya
明かせ love it 存在 know it / いないいないばぁ
Reveal and love it, know my presence / Peek-a-boo
Don't worry 傷つけないよ ライアイア
Don't worry, I won't hurt you, lie-i-ya
I'll let you このミステリーに あいやいやいやい
I'll let you into this mystery, ai-ya-ya-ya-yai
I'll let you さあしみじみより あいやいやいやい
I'll let you, now more deeply, ai-ya-ya-ya-yai
See this finger trap!
Just shout out the spell!
Yeah! Follow the Queen Fox!
時には噛んだりして 痛みを覚えさせて
Sometimes bite me, make me feel the pain
溢れる液体で 汚してよ 全部
Stain everything with spilling fluid
足の先からずっと 這わせたその神経はもう
Those nerves running all the way from my toes...
感触に溺れる 身体 ココロを連れて
...are drowning in sensation, taking my body and heart along
指くわえた我慢の中 欲してんのが理想？
Is desiring while biting my finger the ideal?
いらない 全てはいらない
Don't need it, I don't need any of it
磨き上げてる 邪魔な PRIDE
Polishing this obstructive pride
無意味な世界のルールくらい 無駄としか言い様がない
Worldly rules are so meaningless, there's no way to call them but useless
隠している あなたの STYLE
Your style that you've been hiding
剥ぎ出しに あるがまま DIVE
Dive bare as you are
そこに生まれるのは期待外れなんかじゃない 頂の SMILE
What is born there isn't disappointment, but a supreme smile
吐息を合わせた相性 耳に吹きかける感情
Matching breaths, chemistry, feelings blown into the ear
破裂しそうな胸 騒ぎ出す細胞
Chest about to burst, cells starting to stir
脱ぎかけてるシャツ 優しく裂いてよ
Unbuttoning shirt, tear it gently
まず構わず get フライングも有り 躊躇わないで darlin'
First off, don't mind, get it, jumping the gun is fine, don't hesitate darlin'
自由な世界のど真ん中
Right in the middle of a free world
夢見てんのが本性
Is dreaming my true nature?
いらない 全てはいらない
Don't need it, I don't need any of it
怖気づいた 野望の TRY
A timid attempt at ambition
満足なんそこにない 目に見える哀れな未来
There's no satisfaction there, only a pitiful visible future
思い通りにできる LIFE 手にできるかはあなた次第
A life you can live as you wish, whether you can hold it depends on you
隠したりなんかはしない 誰よりも誇らしげにできる MIND
I won't hide anything, a mind that can be prouder than anyone
ほら この世界の中
Look, in this world
他にはない
There's nothing else
確かなもの
Something certain
自分以外は皆無
Except myself, there is nothing
小さくなってる場合じゃない いつだって No Time!
This is no time to shrink back, there's never time!
ALL RIGHT 上限値超え エンジン全開でいっちゃえ BURN BURN BURN
All right, exceed the limit, full engine ahead, burn burn burn
欲しがってんのはそう 気持ちいいの more...
What you want is that feeling, more...
あるがままの想いで DANCE! イイナリで GET DOWN!
Dance with your true feelings! Obey and get down!
いらない 全てはいらない
Don't need it, I don't need any of it
磨き上げてる 邪魔な PRIDE
Polishing this obstructive pride
無意味な世界のルールくらい 無駄としか言い様がない
Worldly rules are so meaningless, there's no way to call them but useless
隠している あなたの STYLE
Your style that you've been hiding
剥ぎ出しに あるがまま DIVE
Dive bare as you are
そこに生まれるのは期待外れなんかじゃない 頂の SMILE
What is born there isn't disappointment, but a supreme smile
ほら この世界で今
Look, in this world right now
飛び離れて
Leap away
鋭くギラつかせた希望
A sharply glittering hope
もっと本気出していいよ
You can show your true strength even more
Ow!
Huh
Come chase me
Everyday I spent crying 'bout almost-loves turned complicated
On the way, yeah, my heart got torn up, shredded, all but dead and
Now they say I, I'm just a masochist, they're sick of it
Boy, take a hint, you ain't gon' ever get this
Pedal to the metal, shootin' straight to the stars
Got a cravin' like the danger on me (Yeah, she like it like that, like that)
Up another level, temptation you just can't deny
Come get a taste, but can't say I won't bite
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna...
Gonna, ah...
In my eyes, Nirvana, oh, I'm taking off now!
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta run
But it's fun to see you try
So hit me up!
Off the map, I'mma take it, all my energy
So hit me up! Speedin' up fast, ready, target locked
So hit me up! Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece
So hit me up! So hit me up, ah
I never stop
In a new territory, I'm on the edge of glory
Boy, just watch how I move
Gimme that rush
Got no regrets in my mind
Boy, it's on you this time, so hit me up
Outta luck, volume up
You got a crush?
Such a cliché, your bad boy charms, thought I'd fall right back in your arms
Wasn't enough, you needed more, now you're begging to let you score
Surely you'll take it all in stride, I'mma be busy tonight, goodbye, goodbye
Gotta leave you dry
Always tryna play it cool, 20/20 vision on me
Just outside my field of view
Yeah, she like it like that, like that
Engine booming, that's my cue
Catch me if you can, you better keep up the chase, boy, you're falling behind
Supersonic
I'm heading out, I'm gonna (ahh)
In my eyes, Nirvana, oh, I'm taking off now!
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta run
But it's fun to see you try
So hit me up!
Off the map, I'mma take it, all my energy
So hit me up! Speedin' up fast, ready, target locked
So hit me up! Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece
So hit me up! So hit me up, ah
I never stop
In a new territory, I'm on the edge of glory
Boy, just watch how I move
Gimme that rush
Got no regrets in my mind
Boy, it's on you this time, so hit me up
Outta luck, volume up
You got a crush?
Ahh, just barely wasn't enough, you shoulda
Ahh, given me all that you got, you coulda
Coming full circle
I hit a nerve, oh!
Top spot, getting hot
Watch me run it up
So hit me up!
Rev it up and make that vroom vroom vroom vroom
Hit me up!
When I hit you with that zoom zoom zoom zoom
If you know what's good for you, ooh, ooh, ooh
Now I'm back in charge, rise out of the dark
Yeah! I hope you enjoyed that!
Did you guys enjoy? Did you guys enjoy?
We had a couple of songs with a couple of important people,
which I wanna call in to help with this next MC part.
which I want to call in to help with this next MC part.
Special guests! Special guests!
Hey, hey, hey! What's up, 皆さん!
Hey, hey, hey! What's up, everyone!
Yay!
Won't you introduce yourselves, please? Please go ahead.
hololive English CHAD-CAST の森カリオペです！ What's up? ですです。
This is Mori Calliope from hololive English's CHAD-CAST! What's up? Yep yep.
Hey guys, hope you enjoyed our performances!
Hi-Ryus! It's IRyS, also from CHAD-CAST!
Let's go, CHAD-CAST!
Here to rumble! Yeah!
Yeah, what's this movement? Did you say your name? - I said "rumble".
Oh, right! I'm pretty sure she said IRyS, too. Ah, my brain's not working!
It's a big day, guys! - 'Cause she's dancing! - Yeah, it's a big day!
Guys! - Yeah!
Oh yeah! I mean, yeah, obviously, yeah, woo!
What do you think? - It's so cool!
It looks so dynamic! - You look like a K-pop star!
Oh, yeah! I'm so glad you like it!
And look, the MC tail is back! I gotta put it to rest for a little bit, after all that dancing.
So special! - Yeah! But we performed some songs together.
Don't touch it. Don't touch it.
First we had "if..." - Wait!
Oh, well, I guess it's on brand.
Yeah, we know!
Awesome! It's great! - It was a sexy song!
How do you feel about that song? Thank you so much.
How do I feel? Yeah, how do you feel about that song? Feelings, thoughts?
I feel great about it!
I think it was an amazing song!
Impressed with yourself, very good!
So "HIT ME UP"... "HIT ME UP"! - "HIT ME UP"! It's so cool, yeah!
I'm so happy! We practiced so hard! - We practiced so hard.
Yeah, we did! - It was so much fun practicing together though.
Three of us, two of us at a time. It's always fun. - Yeah!
ね！ 楽しかった！
Yeah! That was so fun!
Dancing, happy to be dancing for you guys on my birthday!
Not birthday, birthday but not birthday...
On birthday. Unbirthday!
She's being unbirthed.
But... That sounds so wrong!
Save it for the chat logs, IRyS! Save it for the chat logs!
But after dancing, I am feeling a little bit, you know... hot! Hot!
It's getting hot in here! Is she going to take off her clothes?
Whoa! Age restricted! Maybe not.
I'll be right back!
What is she taking off?
I'm gonna be right back!
Did she take off her pants?!
Why would she take off her pants, IRyS?!
What is she thinking about?!
You need to be stopped!
A manager! Oh, she's coming in.
Whoa! Behold!
I took off my jacket!
Oh my god, she looks so sexy! So cool!
So you can see all my accessories now!
かっこいい！ I love the spiked band! Yeah!
So cool! I love the spiked band! Yeah!
But I have like an arm cuff now as well!
Ah, cool!
Now I can dance even more with no restrictions!
She's even more dynamic!
Yeah, more dynamic!
The pigtails don't get in the way either!
Oh my god, she's popping off! All the arms!
まあ、せっかくなのでね, since we're all here together...
Well, since we're all here together...
How would you guys feel about maybe doing one more song together?
Okay!
I don't have the energy, but I'll do my best!
がんばれ！ がんばれ！ がんばれ！
Do your best! Do your best! Do your best!
You can do it!
That being said, I hope you guys are ready as well. We're gonna bring you one more showcase...
...performance! Let's go!
Ready, set, let's go!
あじまー あじまー あじまー！
Starting! Starting! Starting!
宿題が全ッ然終わらない
My homework isn't finishing at all,
全国のヤバめな諸君！
you risky folks across the country!
時間がなければ 眠らなきゃいいじゃない
If you don't have time, just don't sleep!
がんばれ がんばれ あたし！
Hang in there, hang in there, self!
パーリラ 脳内 フロア
Party time, on my brain's dance floor!
暴れてる カルナバル
A carnival is raging wild!
アドレナリン ドバドバ
Adrenaline gushing out,
究極の PANIGHT
the ultimate PANIGHT!
パリナイ！ パリナイ！ パラパッパ パリナイ！ パリナイ！ パリナイ！ 終わるッナィ！
Party night! Party night! Para-pappa party night! Party night! Party night! Never gonna end!
WE ARE NEGI☆U! WE ARE NEGI☆U! WE ARE NEGI☆U! LET'S GO!
スゴい ヤバい パない 物足りない
Incredible, crazy, insane, not enough!
ない ない 尽くしで とめどない
Overflowing with lack after lack!
スゴい ヤバい パない SATURDAY NIGHT
Incredible, crazy, insane SATURDAY NIGHT!
とにかく もう やるしかない
Anyway, now we just gotta do it!
どすこい ヤバい パない 物足りない 全力 モノ モノ 申したい
Heavy-duty, crazy, insane, not enough, I wanna speak my mind with full power!
たった 一度 の 青春 は
Youth that comes only once in a lifetime,
毎日 ENJOY PARTY NIGHT
enjoy party night every day!
あー お集まりの 旦那様
Ah, gentlemen gathered here,
えー、そうじゃない様、ご唱和ください
and uh, those who aren't, please chant along!
それゆけ SAY
Off you go, SAY:
WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW WOW
D-D-D-DJ!
パッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッ パリナイ！
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa- PARINAI!
EVERYBODY, SING ALONG!
でっち上げ 進化論
Fabricated theory of evolution,
陽キャでも 陰キャでも 勉強だ
introverts or extroverts, it's study time!
WASSUP, WASSUP!
太陽は 銀河系？
Is the sun in the Milky Way?
おしゃべり ノンノンノン！
Chattering is non-non-non!
遊んじゃ ダメダメ ごめんなさーい！
Playing around is a big no-no, I'm so sorry!
朝が来て 眠れない
Morning comes and I can't sleep,
どうしよう
what should I do?
神様も 両手 挙げて FLY HIGH
Even God raises both hands to FLY HIGH!
なんとかするしかない
Gotta manage somehow!
頑張れ 出来るって
"Hang in there, you can do it,"
ド派手に カマしちゃうね ネバギバ PUT YOUR HANDS UP
making a flashy impact, NEVER GIVE UP, PUT YOUR HANDS UP!
タリナイ！ タリナイ！ ターラタッタ タリナイ！ タリナイ！ タリナイ！ 時間がない！
Not enough! Not enough! Ta-ra-tatta not enough! Not enough! Not enough! No time left!
WE ARE NEGI☆U! WE ARE NEGI☆U! WE ARE NEGI☆U! LET'S GO!
LET'S GO!
スゴい ヤバい パない 物足りない
Incredible, crazy, insane, not enough!
代打の バッター かたじけない
Pinch hitter, my apologies!
スゴい ヤバい パない SUNDAY NIGHT
Incredible, crazy, insane SUNDAY NIGHT!
とにかく もう やるしかない
Anyway, now we just gotta do it!
どすこい ヤバい パない 物足りない 宿題 やっぱり 終わらない
Heavy-duty, crazy, insane, not enough, homework really isn't finishing!
たった 一度 の 青春 は
Youth that comes only once in a lifetime,
脳内 HAPPY PARTY NIGHT
happy party night inside my brain!
IRyS、Calli、Bae！
IRyS, Calli, Bae!
この問題全然わかんないんですけど！
I don't understand this problem at all!
えーッ！ 何その鉛筆！ めっちゃ可愛いジャン、いいなー！
Eh! What's with that pencil?! It's super cute, so jealous!
でしょー！ キラキラ光るんですよー！
Right?! It sparkles and shines!
えー、へへ、みんな、元気だなー
Eh, hehe, everyone's so energetic.
陽キャって、こんな時もすごいなー
Extroverts are amazing even at times like this.
Yeah yeah, party party!
お書きになったそんな音楽は現在使用されておりません。
We're sorry, but the music you've written is no longer in use.
もう一度お書き直しください。
Please try rewriting it once more.
意味わかんねえ
I'll never get this!
どうせ誰も聴いてなんかないさ
Dosed and shallow like fashion after the trend
音楽なんて全部ファッション
Pumping passionless to the fans
音楽なんて選手退場ワンナイト
Treated like a lover that lasts one night
どうせ何も伝えてなんかないさ
Artless palpable prop to flesh out the brand
なんとなくトック撮って売名
Write a song to dance to, and bam
あんな気取って置いて最低グンナイ
All the pretentiousness, I hate it, good night
どうしたってどうみたって尊師たちでもう大渋滞
Try to fit and try to shine, but we're in a universe of big stars
それでもあっち、こっち、そっち、ぼっち、卍Zエイジ豚も欲しがる
I took a look to find they're all alike from manji, Z, to even the depressed and junky
パンチライン欲しいの
Something cool with a beat
意味とかどっちだっていいよ
I don't need to understand what it means
歌詞とかどうでもいいのでノれるのください
I want to go hard and sing like I don't care if the lyrics right
さぁ皆で笑いましょう
Sit back and now enjoy the show
芸術より数の大小？
This song will make the view count explode
ヴァイラスに酷い代償
The virus altered the world we know
じゃあどうすんの？それでいいんだっけ？
That's the way it is / But why always like this?
頭は空回り死んでいく
Growing tired of the things that I love to do
ふざけるなバイバイバズメロディー
So fuck it, I'll say bye bye buzzing melodies
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
And burn through all the lie lie copying machines
化けんな幻想でも理想でも良い
You lose yourself in what you're pretending to be
君のいたかった物はどうしたんだい？
Can we go back to back to what we had at the start?
ざまでもオーライ嘘じゃない
Forget about if it's not how you want to be
お金や擬奏で満たす前に
We're living in a world that's void of honesty
負けんな覚醒せよ鼓動達よ
The earth stands still when we only get what we need
君の伝えたかった物はどうしたんだい？
Somebody start to set the precedent and restart
意味わかんねぇ！
I'll never get this!
お書きになったそんな音楽は現在使用されておりません
We're sorry, but the music you've written is no longer in use
ポップソング、ヒットソング聴いてもう一度お書き直しください
Please refer to the most recent pop music releases, and try again
あーもうハイカラ作家ばッカ 洒落臭いわ はぁ...
Ah... more trends and actors / They all wanna look the same, huh
どいつもしこいつもしそいつもしあいつもし
Another one, nother one, nother one, nother one
意味わかんねぇ！
I'll never get this!
どうしたってどうみたって尊師たちでもう大渋滞 それでもあっちこっちそっちぼっち卍Zエイジ豚も欲しがる
Try to fit and try to shine, but we're in a universe of big stars / I took a look to find they're all alike from manji, Z, to even the depressed and junky
パンチライン欲しいの 意味とかどっちだっていいよ
Something cool with a beat / I don't need to understand what it means
歌詞とかどうでもいいので伸びるのください
I want to blow up and sing like I don't care if the lyrics right
さぁ皆で祓いましょう 芸術より数なんでしょう？
Sit back and just enjoy the show / Don't you wanna see the view count explode
ヴァイラスに酷い代償
The virus altered the world we know
じゃあどうすんの？それでいいんだっけ？
That's the way it is / But why always like this?
頭は空回り死んでいく
Growing tired of the things that I love to do
ふざけるなバイバイバズメロディー
So fuck it, I'll say bye bye buzzing melodies
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
And burn through all the lie lie copying machines
化けんな幻想でも理想でも良い
You lose yourself in what you're pretending to be
君の歌いたかった物はどうしたんだい？
Can we go back to back to what we had at the start?
このままじゃ到底終われない
We're going in a loop that I only wanna leave
欲しいのはきっとお金じゃない
I know it's not a price that should value our dreams
負けんな覚醒せよ鼓動達よ
The earth stands still when we only get what we need
君の歌いたかった物がきっとあるんだ
I know there must be others waiting for a new start
ふざけるな...
So fuck it, I'll say...
ふざけるな！バイバイバズメロディー
Yeah, fuck it, I'll say bye bye buzzing melodies
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
And burn through all the lie lie copying machines
化けんな幻想でも理想でも良い
You lose yourself in what you're pretending to be
君の歌いたかった物はどうしたんだい？
Can we go back to back to what we had at the start?
ざまでもオーライ嘘じゃない
Forget about if it's not how you want to be
お金や擬奏で満たす前に
We're living in a world that's void of honesty
負けんな覚醒せよ鼓動達よ
The earth stands still when we only get what we need
僕の伝えたかった物はどうしたんだい？
Somebody start to set the precedent and restart
意味わかんねぇ！
I'll never get this!
意味わかんねぇよ！
I really don't at all!
意味わかんねぇ！
I'll never get this!
Virtual blah blah blah blah？ I'm a V.
Virtual blah blah blah blah? I'm a V.
Virtual blah blah blah blah？ I'm a V だ la vida な diva.
Virtual blah blah blah blah? I'm a V, da la vida na diva.
Love that blah blah blah.
たかだか生裸の魂
At best, a mere bare soul
触らば可愛いのコントン
If touched, is cuteness just a scam?
高天原から ほら「堕としてあげる」
From high above, see? "I'll let you fall"
はい そう メンヘラでも面がキュートならメンキラー
Yeah, even if mentally ill, if the face is cute, a total man-killer
とか貼られたレッテル 逝ってるメンタルは
The labels placed on me, my dying mentality is...
最強スマイルで転がしていけファンダム
Rolling over the fandom with the ultimate smile
誤魔化してる傷心性根
Deceiving a wounded heart and true nature
晒されたら引退にゃんてな
If exposed, it's retirement, or something like that
I am a V, I'm a V, I'm a 泡々よ
I am a V, I'm a V, I'm bubbling up
I am la vida な diva 淫らは嫌よ
I am la vida, a diva, I hate indecency
夢見てる少年a 夢見てる少女a
Dreaming Boy A, Dreaming Girl A
Vならvidaは甘々甘々の？ No！
If you're a V, is life all sweet and easy? No!
ちょん切る我利我利妄想
Severing selfish, greedy delusions
笑わせんな我がセンター
Don't make me laugh, I'm the center
誰よりも客寄せのパンダ
A crowd-pleasing panda more than anyone else
吾は何だ？
What am I?
まるで膿んだ自己愛性勝者
Like a festered narcissistic survivor
Am I V？ Am I C？
Am I V? Am I C?
洗いざらい甘い汁搾いに
Extracting all the sweet juice completely
我愛你, so love me.
I love you, so love me.
Now love me
惚れ直し Hey Monster
Fall for me again, hey monster
Oh my name is Love Love 愛でられたなら 吐くまで Love Talk
Oh my name is Love Love, if you cherish me, love talk till you puke
I'm a Leader 成り上がり Winner 心の中 Smooth like butter
I'm a leader, a self-made winner, inside my heart smooth like butter
Touch me したいならほら えんどれ
If you wanna touch me, here, go endlessly
Catch me The high-piece 召し上がる姿が分からない Wow!
Catch me, the high-piece, I can't even tell how you'll consume it, wow!
我の心叫ぶひとつの Light
My heart cries out to a single light
生きる姿与えた魂を今
The soul that gave form to life, right now
二つにして愛をバラバラに
split it in two and tear love to pieces.
生まれた時の喜びはもう...
The joy from when I was born is already...
承知
understood.
サヨナラでいいの
Is goodbye really enough?
ダメね
No way.
Watch out, watch out
Watch out, what make-up make-up
Like 勘の感ね
Like intuition's feeling, right?
アララ 敏感で共感ね
Oh my, so sensitive, sympathizing, right?
絶対 招待ね アラ
It's an absolute invitation, oh my
Watch out, what make-up make-up
Like 勘の感ね
Like intuition's feeling, right?
アララ 敏感で共感ね
Oh my, so sensitive, sympathizing, right?
いい感の終わりだね
It's the end of a good vibe, right?
アラ Minta Kira
Oh, Minta Kira
I am a V, I'm a V, I'm a Our Our Yo
I am La Vida, My Diva ミダラ ワヤ Yo
I am La Vida, My Diva, Midara Waya Yo
夢見てる少年が
A dreaming boy
夢見てる少女で
is a dreaming girl,
V なら Vida Our Our Our Our No
if it's V, it's Vida Our Our Our Our No
教養さ
It's common sense,
子供の頃言われたもんだ
something I was told as a child.
あのヒーローショーの人形の背中にゃ
"On the back of the hero show figure,
チャックついてないから開くな！
there's no zipper, so don't open it!"
Virtual だ Human だ
Whether virtual or human,
忍びのこの世が
in this world of stealth,
存在は ワンワンダー
existence is a one-wonder!
掘っても掘っても死ぬまでバラバラだ！
No matter how deep you dig, we're pieces till we die!
Watch out, watch out
Are you ready for...?
惚れたら死ぬぞ
If you fall for me, you'll die!
Watch out, love love...
I am a V!
Sky-high!
I'm so tired!
I hope you guys have been enjoying the show!
We had so many bangers after bangers after bangers!
A lot of dancing.
We had PSYCHO.
We had CYBERPUNK DEAD BOY.
We had V.
My arms are dead, everything dead.
But that's not the end of the show yet,
we gotta keep going on and on and on and on and on!
And here I bring you a very, very, very important
and exciting announcement.
I am about to perform a song that no one has heard before!
No one, except for me,
because it's my new song!
I've been hyping this up for a while now,
because I'm really, really excited,
and this will be the first time
that I'm sharing it with all of you.
So I hope you enjoy.
More information after I perform it, 'cause you gotta see it first, you know?
Wish me luck.
I'm nervous, but...
We got this!
これから...
From here on out...
新曲です！
It's a new song!
めっちゃ緊張してるんだけど
I'm super nervous, but...
頑張って
I'll do my best
パフォーマンスしたいと思います！
to give it my best performance!
どうぞ！
Please enjoy!
준비~!
Get ready~!
That's good game, what a shame.
Players, they all complain,
"Why me?", "No, not again!"
Shout! Ratatata~ but!
Ain't got time, so dry those eyes
Look around, what's that I spy?
The broken and bruised
All got something to prove now
Abracadabra, let's go
Watch them like dice as they fall
끝까지 가보자 go
Let's go all the way to the end, go
나는 내 맘대로 해, hey
I do whatever I want, hey
Double one, double win
Lowly to lottery
Do or die
We hit that high
Snake eyes, snake eyes
Come on now, don't be shy
뜨겁게 달아올라 (불타올라)
Heating up hot (burning up)
놀자 all day all night
Let's play all day, all night
So turn it up, can't stop, won't stop preachin'
Who said the sky's the limit?
Show them that we mean business
We are the young and vicious
Snake eyes, they never lie
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
지겨워!
Sick of it!
우리들의 광란의 party
Our wild, crazy party
보여줄게 환상 safari
I'll show you a fantasy safari
Baddie baddie, nobody can stop me
끼리끼리 붙어, come on closer!
Birds of a feather stick together, come on closer!
Go! Go! 더 빠르게
Go! Go! Even faster
Actin' all naughty
싹 다 부셔 모조리
Smash it all, every single bit
모조리 싹 다 다다다!
Every single bit, all of it!
Shut your mouth, will come back down
Ready the fight
Ready the screaming
Abracadabra let's go
Watch it we reapin' it all
(reapin' it all)
꺾이지 않는 의지 될대로 돼 볼래 play
Unbending will, let's play and see what happens
Reason, our demon, believe in the beat and
Just wait and see
We hit that high
Snake eyes, snake eyes
Come on now don't be shy
뜨겁게 달아올라 (불타올라)
Heating up hot (burning up)
놀자 all day all night (all day all night)
Let's party all day all night (all day all night)
Let the beat drop!
Go!
We go hard
기사회생 전부를 걸어 bet
Resurrection from the dead, bet everything
Go! We go hard
I want it all
다시 일어나 파괴와 재생
Rise again, destruction and rebirth
죽지 않아, 전부 걸어
I won't die, bet it all
맞서 싸워, 시작이야
Fight back, this is the start
Take the crown
끝까지 달려가
Run until the end
Rule the game
We'll hit that high
Snake eyes, snake eyes
Come on now don't be shy
같이 춤을 춰 봐, 이렇게
Dance with me like this
멈출 순 없어 같이 dance all night
Can't stop, let me dance all night with you
준비~!
Get ready~!
Don't be afraid of losing
It's just a new beginning
Look at the cards we dealing
Sometimes it takes a villain
Snake eyes, the time is nigh
Fly high with pride and leave all fears behind!
It's finally out!
I hope you all enjoyed my new song, Snake Eyes! Snake Eyes, Snake Eyes, Snake Eyes, Snake Eyes!
This has been such a long process in the making. I can't even talk! I'm exhausted, but also I'm so happy!
It's finally out! My newest song, Snake Eyes, was what I just performed! Not only is it...
...not the first time that, you know, I've written a lot of the lyrics from scratch,
you know, but also it's the first time choreographing a multi-member song, with the two back dancers!
I'm so happy! I did it!
I hope you guys enjoyed it!
Now, very important, pay attention! The MV of this new song is also going to be premiering very soon after the live is over!
And it is going to be my first-ever 3D music video! Yeah!
もう超楽しみ！やっとね、新曲がちょっとね、あのー、公開するので、
I'm so excited! Finally, my new song is being released, so...
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです。
I'm super happy.
えっと、この後、ライブの後ね、あのー、初の3D MVもプレミアするので、
So after this live stream, my first 3D MV will premiere,
あのー、観ててください！お願いします！
so please watch it! Please!
歌詞、えー、英語の歌詞はほぼあの、自分で書いたので、
I wrote almost all of the English lyrics myself,
あの、あと韓国語もね、あの、頑張ってたんで、
and I also worked hard on the Korean parts too, so...
あの、聴いてください！
please give it a listen!
Streaming will also begin shortly after as well.
It should be local... local time meaning that I never know anything, but it'll happen soon!
So please make sure to check it out afterwards!
Phew! I hope I did okay. I don't know, I was stressed about the choreography for a very long time, but...
Now is time! It's the thing you've all been waiting for!
Merch showcase!
グッズの紹介に入りたいと思います！
I'd like to move on to the merch showcase!
This is the lineup for this time!
Ta-da! Woo!
Baelz Hakos 2026 Birthday Live... birthday merch! Birthday merch is what the full set looks like!
フルセットはこんな感じです！
This is what the full set looks like!
And let me... let's look at them one by one. This is what the full set looks like, and then we can go through them one by one.
What do we have first? First up, 最初は...
What do we have first? First up, first is...
何でしょう？
What could it be?
Woo! We have the [ReCOLOR] Rubber Mat! Look at that beauty!
Um, this illustration is of course by my beloved Mama...
Mika Pikazo-sensei! 今年もね、書いてくださりありがとうございます。
Mika Pikazo-sensei! Thank you so much for drawing it again this year.
Um, I just thought, you know, my very first birthday merch was also, actually had like a rubber mat in it.
And since, you know, I have a new outfit, I thought it was only fitting that, you know, we have another rubber mat for me to switch out.
I really wanted this, so that's why... That's why I wanted it! And you know, you can use it for HoloCa...
Oh, also look at a new desk mat.
Oh, also look at the new desk mat.
And it's really pretty, look at it.
Look at it! It's so pretty! Thank you so much!
あの、ママ... 今年もね、Mikaママに、あの、イラスト描いてくださったので、本当に
Mika-mama drew the illustration for me again this year!
ありがとうございます！ぜひぜひ買ってください！
Thank you so much! Please be sure to check it out!
And, well, what's the next item? Second is...
Tada!
The ReCOLOR Plushie Keychain, designed after my new outfit!
I've always wanted like a... a mini, you know, plushie that... that I came out with.
I've always wanted like a... a mini, you know, plushie that I came out with.
I think it was strictly fitting, cause I have a new outfit, and I wanted a plushie in the new outfit. I can take her around places, you know.
I think it was strictly fitting, cause I have a new outfit, and I wanted a plushie in the new outfit that you can take around places.
And, you know, you can photograph her, chuck her, pat her, whatever you want to do.
But it's a plushie keychain, so it comes with a ball chain so you can attach it to your bag!
Isn't she so cute?
Look at those squishy cheeks!
めっちゃ可愛いでしょ？キー... あの
Isn't it super cute? Um,
ぬいぐるみキーホルダーなので、なんかカバンにつけたりとかね、できるので
since it's a plushie keychain, you can attach it to your bag or something,
めちゃくちゃ可愛い感じになりました！ありがとうございます！
so it turned out super cute! Thank you so much!
えーっと、次！What is the next one?
Uh, next! What is the next one?
これです！
This one!
The Lil Plushie Shed Pouch!
It is a pouch. It is a pouch for the plushie, if you get both, it's like a set, you know, because...
It is a pouch for the plushie. If you get both, it's like a set, you know, because...
You know, you want to take your little Bae out into the world, but what if she gets dirty, you know?
You don't want her to get snagged on a corner and she rips. You gotta protect your little Bae!
You don't want her to get snagged on a corner and rip. You gotta protect your little Bae!
So, you have a Lil Plushie Shed to house your little Bae!
Um, but it fits perfectly, and, you know, you can use it. The design is also really cool as well.
Um, next! Last but not least...
is something very special. It is a voice pack!
But, it is my first ever ASMR voice pack!
Um... I get really embarrassed doing ASMR stuff, but I just thought, you know...
Since it's a special occasion, maybe it'd be nice to have my very first ASMR voice pack.
It features an intimate scene with you guys after the live show.
So, if you want to, you know, check it out, please do!
僕、初、初のASMRボイス、シナリオボイスなので
It's my very first ASMR scenario voice pack,
もし気になってる方はぜひ聴いてください！
so if you're interested, please be sure to listen to it!
ありがとうございます！It's called "Forever Your Bae".
Thank you so much! It's called "Forever Your Bae".
恥ずかしい...
I'm embarrassed...
Anyway, here are the full set purchase bonuses!
Tada!
The postcard! You get a limited edition which features a hand-signed autograph and handwritten message from yours truly, just an extra way to say thank you very much.
The postcard! You get a limited edition which features a hand-signed autograph and handwritten message from yours truly, just an extra way to say thank you.
And, the standard version comes with the foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message!
Arm's about to... about to die, but it's all right! Thank you so much!
Arm's about to die, but it's all right! Thank you so much!
えーっと、特... 特... 特徴... やばい、読め... 漢字が何だっけ？あの...
Um, special... features... Oh no, I can't read... What was this kanji again? Um...
特典はこちらです！ありがとうございます！
The purchase bonus is this! Thank you so much!
ポストカード、えーっと、あの、直筆... 直筆...
The postcard has, um, a handwritten...
サインとメッセージがあります！ありがとうございます！
autograph and message! Thank you so much!
Oh my god, my brain is just... it's gone. I'm so tired. But anyway, um...
I think that's it. Oh wait, no! There's also a bonus voice... wait, I forgot!
So with the full set, there is a bonus voice pack that is also ASMR, that's on top of the already ASMR voice pack,
So with the full set, there is a bonus voice pack that is also ASMR, on top of the already ASMR voice pack,
just a little extra thing to say thank you.
That's it. I'm embarrassed. Anyway, yes!
そういうことです！ありがとうございます！はい！
So that's how it is! Thank you so much! Yes!
Um, yes.
Before we continue, I guess... um, there is a little bit after, so I'm gonna go put my jacket on real quick,
if that's okay. I'll be right back. ちょっと着替えてきます！
if that's okay. I'll be right back. I'll go change real quick!
じゃーん！戻ってきました！はい！
Ta-da! I'm back! Yes!
上着です！えーっと、just put on my jacket.
Here's my jacket! Um, just put on my jacket.
I'm so happy that, you know, I got to do a birthday live this year even though it's not really my birthday.
Um, I'm so happy that I got to show my new outfit. I'm just happy that I got a new outfit!
It's so easy to dance in, I love the way it looks, and today I got to dance with so many of my friends!
It was so much fun! Got to challenge myself.
It's always an amazing, amazing experience being able to do a birthday live.
いや、今年ね、あの、いっぱいメンバーと一緒に踊ってめちゃくちゃ嬉しくて、もう新衣装もめちゃくちゃ嬉しくて、もうとにかく嬉しいです！
Dancing with so many members made me super happy, and I'm super happy with my new outfit too, I'm just overall so happy!
あの、みんなもね、a lot of planning that goes into these, um, all the staff and everyone, スタッフさんもね、みんなもね
A lot of planning goes into these, all the staff and everyone, all the staff and all of you too!
Everyone's
力
...power...
が、必要
...is needed.
もうなんだこれ、もう英語か日本語かもう分かんないっすね
Gosh, what is this? I don't even know if I'm speaking English or Japanese anymore.
すいません、はい
Sorry, yes.
I'm just mixing up my languages, but...
Please do check out...
...the new song MV that's coming out shortly.
I'm really, really proud of it.
Um, but that's kind of it. That's all I have for today.
BUT!
There is a final encore song that I wanted to sing...
...that I think really sums up today's live.
So if you would like to stay, please stay to the end.
Please listen. Please don't go anywhere.
ちょっとこの後、最後の1曲あります。
There's one last song coming up after this.
今日のテーマにぴったりの曲だと思いますので
I think it's the perfect song for today's theme,
最後まで聞いてください。
so please listen until the very end.
はい！
Alright!
あと新曲のMVも見てくださいね、はい。
Also, please check out the new song's MV too, yes.
はい、あ、じゃあ最後の曲、ラスト曲、どうぞ！
Yes, ah, then the last song, the final track, here you go!
魂の色は何色ですか
What color is your soul?
Thank you for coming to my live today!
I hope I brought some color to your day!
最後まで盛り上がっていこうぜ！
Let's get hyped until the very end!
「もういっそ 折れたままで」
"I'd rather stay broken..."
捨てるほど 逃げ出すほど
So much that I'd throw it away or run,
強くないよ ほら
I'm not that strong, look...
もう一度 鼓動、高鳴る
Once more, my heartbeat quickens
何が正しいかなんて 分からないけど
I don't know what's right, but...
形のないものばかりが
Only the intangible things...
大切になっていく
...are becoming important to me.
飾らない言葉だけが
Only unadorned words...
強く結ばれてる
...are strongly tied together.
また躓いて 転がって それでも砕けない
Tripping and stumbling again, yet still unbroken
魂の色は 何色ですか
What color is the soul?
ただ傷ついて 強がって それでも見つけたいよ
Just getting hurt and acting tough, but I still want to find it
魂のカタチ 確かめてるよ
Confirming the shape of the soul
深い地の底で一人 扉と鍵を探す
Alone deep underground, searching for the door and key
おとぎ話は ほら 泡の様に全部消えて
Look, fairy tales all fade away like bubbles
葛藤 残像だけ 次の頁へ
Conflict and afterimages lead to the next page
伸びてく枝葉が分かれて
Spreading branches split...
それぞれの道を行く
...and take their own separate paths.
寂しい思い出だけが
Only lonely memories...
強く根を張ってる
...are taking deep root.
また貫いて 失って それでも挫けない
Pierced and losing again, yet still unyielding
心はどこに 器はどこに
Where is the heart? Where is the vessel?
ただ残されて 抜け落ちて それでも伝えたいよ
Just left behind and falling away, yet I still want to convey it
魂の日々を 魂の意志を
The days of the soul, the will of the soul
ずっと ずっと...
Forever and ever...
魂の色は...
What color is...
何色ですか
...the color of the soul?
赤色ですか...
Is it red...?
青色ですか
...or is it blue?
魂の色は... 魂の色は...
The color of the soul... The color of the soul...
何色ですか... 何色ですか...
What color is it...? What color is it...?
透明な過去に 不透明な明日に
In a transparent past, in an opaque tomorrow
生きるあなたは 何色ですか
Living as you are, what color are you?
また躓いて 転がって それでも砕けない
Tripping and stumbling again, yet still unbroken
魂の色は 何色ですか
What color is the soul?
ただ傷ついて 強がって それでも見つけたいよ
Just getting hurt and acting tough, but I still want to find it
魂のカタチ 確かめてるよ
Confirming the shape of the soul
たしかめたるよ
I've made sure,
ずっと
always,
歌
this song...
ずっと
Always,
歌
this song...
ずっと
Always,
歌
this song...
ずっと
Always,
歌
this song...